<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Prologue on</title><link>https://appifysheets.com/docs/prologue/</link><description>Recent content in Prologue on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://appifysheets.com/docs/prologue/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introduction</title><link>https://appifysheets.com/docs/prologue/introduction/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://appifysheets.com/docs/prologue/introduction/</guid><description>What we are all about We build professional Web/Desktop applications for managers who are frustrated with Google Sheets/Excel in a month. How to get started Press the link 👈 to schedule a free consultation session with us where we help you identify your painpoints and give you a direction to move toward, whether we can help you or not.
How our services work The goal is to help you and your team transition from Google Sheets (or Excel) to a functioning Web Application that fully replaces your Google Sheets / Excel workflow within 4 weeks with additional 4 weeks of support.</description></item><item><title>Quick Start</title><link>https://appifysheets.com/docs/prologue/quick-start/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 13:59:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://appifysheets.com/docs/prologue/quick-start/</guid><description>Hello, My name is Zura! And this is my first ever attempt at GitHub
This is my second attempt. Zura speaking again! Doks uses npm to centralize dependency management, making it easy to update resources, build tooling, plugins, and build scripts:
Download and install Node.js (it includes npm) for your platform. Start a new Doks project Create a new site, change directories, install dependencies, and start development server.</description></item><item><title>Commands</title><link>https://appifysheets.com/docs/prologue/commands/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://appifysheets.com/docs/prologue/commands/</guid><description>💡 You can change the commands in the scripts section of `./package.json`. create Create new content for your site:
npm run create [path] [flags] See also the Hugo docs: hugo new.
lint Check scripts, styles, and markdown for errors:
npm run lint scripts Check scripts for errors:
npm run lint:scripts [-- --fix] styles Check styles for errors:
npm run lint:styles [-- --fix] markdown Check markdown for errors:</description></item></channel></rss>